https://ohiosteelheaders.com/ohio-fishing/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders Privacy Policy Sections
This Privacy Policy applies to Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders and its affiliates (collectively, “Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders,” “O.C.B.S.,” “our,” “us,” or “we”) and describes how Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders collects, uses and shares customer information from our websites, mobile websites, mobile applications, and the services provided by us in connection with the sites and applications that link to this Privacy Policy. It also provides guidance on how you can manage the personal information that you provide to us. Please also read our full Privacy Policy.
Personal Information Collected
When you use our services or make a purchase, you voluntarily share certain personal information with us such as your name, e-mail address, address, mobile number, and/or credit/debit card information and, with your prior permission, when you connect through social media networks. Read more…
Tracking Technologies (cookies, etc.)
We use tracking technologies such as cookies and similar technologies to measure usage during your visits to our services and provide information and advertising that will be of most interest and benefit to you. More Info…
Targeted Advertising
Third party ad networks may also use information gathered from your use of the services to serve targeted, interest based advertisements to you on websites and mobile applications. More Info
Use and Sharing of Information
We may share your information gathered from your use of the services with our marketing partners, affiliated companies, our service providers, mobile carriers, social networks, legal and law enforcement, and others if there is a change of control, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. More Info
Effective Date: November 11, 2019
Your Information Access and Managing Options
You can change your personal information by clicking “My Account” (if available), or by contacting us. We may retain the information collected for the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may also retain certain information for purposes outlined in the Privacy Policy, such as for archival purposes and if required by law. More Info…
Your Information Choices
You can control if you want to receive promotional communications from us. Learn more…
Arbitration
Any disputes under this Privacy Policy will be resolved in accordance binding arbitration as outlined in the Terms.
Updates to this Privacy Policy
You agree that we may notify you about material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting a new “Effective Date” on the Privacy Policy. More Info…
Your California Privacy Rights
California customer? Learn Info…
Contact Us
Questions about our Privacy Policy or your information collected may be sent to Support@OhioSteelheaders.com or as otherwise set forth in the Privacy Policy. More Info…
Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders Privacy Policy
Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders has developed this Privacy Policy which details important information regarding the use and disclosure of user information collected on Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders owned or controlled websites, mobile sites and applications, and related services, communications and tools that link to this Privacy Policy, and when you interact offline with Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders regarding those sites, applications and related services and tools (collectively referred to as the “Services”).
Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue to use the Services and the choices we offer for you to manage the information we collect related to the use of the Services. Each time that you access or use the Services, you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy.
If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy or Terms of Service (“Terms”), which are incorporated into this Privacy Policy by reference and govern your use of our Services, please discontinue accessing or using the Services.
1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT.
Information Collected Directly From You
You can browse our Services without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information including but not limited to your name, email address, phone number, mobile telephone number, credit card information or physical contact information about yourself. If you create an account, contact us or purchase any of our Services you choose to give us your personal information and are not anonymous to us.
When you register an account, or use certain of our Services you may provide certain additional information such as username and e-mail address. You may also provide payment information such as credit or debit card information, name and billing address to purchase a membership, series, collections or libraries.
Information Imported from Social Networks
We will collect information from you when you interact with our Services through third party social networking services (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Google+) (each and collectively, a “Social Network”). You may also have the option to consent to connecting your activity on our Services with your Social Network information and activity.
If you permit a connection, we and that Social Network may be able to identify you and associate information received pursuant to the connection with information we already have about you. Please review the Social Network’s privacy policy and choices for sharing information of any Social Network connected to our Services.
Surveys and Promotions
From time-to-time we may request information from you and other users via surveys, or contests, sweepstakes or other promotions. Participation is completely voluntary. Information collected may be used as set forth in this Privacy Policy and as set forth in the applicable terms or official rules, including without limitation to notify the winners and award prizes, and file winners’ information as required by law. Survey information will be used for the purposes of the survey.
Information You Post/Social Networks
The Services are designed to enable you to communicate with others and any information or content you post when participating with the Services and Social Networks, plug ins or other applications becomes public information, depending upon your privacy settings, and is subject to redistribution by Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders and other third parties. There is no expectation of privacy when posting content or otherwise participating in such interactive forums and we have no control over how those users may use the information you make public. Therefore, you should exercise caution and discretion when deciding to disclose your personal information in a submission or posting.
Mobile Devices
We may collect additional information from you if you access our Services through a mobile device; for example, your unique device identifier, device’s operating system, mobile carrier, location, and if you opt-in, geo-location. We may also collect your location information from your IP address or zip code. We may also use location data internally or in conjunction with our third party service providers to customize your experience and provide offers that may be relevant to you. The degree to which your location can be identified depends on the device you are using, e.g. laptop, smartphone, tablet or other access device (each a “Device”) and how you are connected to the internet (e.g. via cable broadband connection, WiFi, etc.).
Information about Others/Inviting Friends
From time to time you may choose to submit personal information about other people to invite them to join a Service. Inviting friends is always optional. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on the Services, your e-mail address may be included in the communication sent to your friend.
2. INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES.
Tracking Technologies
In addition to any information that you choose tosubmit to us, we and our business partners may use a variety of tracking technologies such as cookies, flash cookies, web beacons/GIFs, HTML5, embedded scripts, e-tags/cache browsers/web logs (“Tracking Technologies”), that automatically (or passively) collect certain information from your browser/device whenever you visit or interact with the Services or third party websites. This information may include your Device identifier, the type and version of Internet browser software you use, and your operating system. We may also collect password information from you when you log in, as well as computer and connection information. During some visits, we may use these tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, time spent on certain pages and page interaction information. Certain features of our Services are only available through the use of Tracking Technologies. You may encounter tracking technologies/cookies from our third party service providers that we have allowed on our Services who assist us with various aspects of our operations and Services. Tracking Technologies are used for a variety of purposes, including the following:
Your Secure Browsing Experience.
We may use operationally necessary Tracking Technologies for system administration, to prevent fraudulent activity, to improve security and to allow you to make use of our Services.
Website Performance
We may use Tracking Technologies to assess the performance of our Services, including as part of our analytic practices to optimize content offered through the Services.
Overall Functionality
We may use Tracking Technologies to tell us, for example, whether you have visited the Services before or if you are a new visitor, and to help us identify the features in which you may have the greatest interest.
Your Interests & Preferences.
We may use Tracking Technologies to deliver content, including ads, relevant to your interests on the Services and third party sites based on how you interact with our advertisements or content, as well as to track the content you access.
Location and Geo-location Functionality
Information gathered from your use of the Services may be combined with information from third-party sources to identify your location by state and region (“Regional Location”). If you enable location services for our Services we may collect regional location data periodically as you use or leave open our Services. Certain of our mobile applications have search functionality that gathers aggregate location data about visitors and when visitors opt in, allows us to collect information about their precise geographic location (“Geo-location”).
We may use GPS, Wi-Fi, Bluetooth or cell tower proximity to determine geo-location. If you agree to have your Geo-location collected, we may use and retain that precise location data to provide you with information about our Services or carry out marketing and other activities contemplated by our mobile applications and by this Policy.
When you have Geo-location software running on your Device, we may only collect that information as controlled by your privacy settings on your Device. For most mobile Devices, you are able to withdraw your permission for us to acquire this information on your location through the Device settings.
If you have questions about how to disable your mobile Device’s location services, we recommend you contact your mobile Device service provider or the Device manufacturer.
3. TARGETED ADVERTISING.
Interest Based Advertising
We may use Tracking Technologies to collect information about your visits over time and across the Services and other third party web sites, as well as information received from other sources, in order to serve more targeted advertising to you. To serve our ads, we use a variety of third party advertising service providers, including networks, data exchanges, ad servers, analytics providers and others.
These third parties may use Tracking Technologies to send directly to your Device the advertisements and links that appear on the Services. They automatically receive your Device identifier when this happens. Their tools may also limit the number of times you see the same ad and help measure the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.
These third parties may also use information gathered from your use of the Services to serve targeted, interest based advertisements to you on third party websites and applications. Some of the advertising service providers may be members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies. If you opt out of receiving targeted ads in this manner, you will continue to receive advertising messages, but they will not be customized to you based on your use of the Services and third party websites.
If you would like more information about advertisers’ use of tracking technologies and about your option not to accept them, you can go to www.networkadvertising.org. To learn more about how interest-based information is collected, whether the companies we use are part of an industry network regarding behavioral advertising, or to know your choices about not having information used in this manner, you can go to www.aboutads.info.
Please note that the opt-out is cookie-based and will only affect the specific computer or mobile application, and browser or operating system, on which the opt-out is applied. You can also accept or decline cookies through your browser settings. To learn more, please look at the cookie settings available in your specific web browser(s).
Browser “Do Not Track” Signals
Some third party browsers provide “do not track” machine readable signals for websites, which are automatically applied by default and therefore do not necessarily reflect our visitors’ choice as to whether they wish to receive advertisements tailored to their interests. As a result, we do not respond to these signals and Services will function normally.
4. HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION.
Our Use of Information
We may use information that we collect about you: (1) to respond to your requests; (2) to fulfill orders; (3) to provide customer service; (4) to administer surveys, sweepstakes or other promotions; (5) to improve and customize our Services; (6) to provide information to a third party at your request; (7) to give you information about your account or our Services; (8) for internal business purposes; (9) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information, or (10) as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.
Service Providers
We may disclose information to our third party service providers in order to monitor the activity of the Services, conduct surveys, administer contests or sweepstakes, send marketing communications, and to provide other Services to you, such as provide customer service.
Process Payments
Information may be disclosed to process credit card transactions, which are securely handled by established third party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process your order. In addition, we may disclose information to third parties to verify the authenticity of any financial transaction involving our company or its subsidiaries or to update your billing information.
Co-branded Areas
Certain areas on our Services may be provided to you in association with third parties who often provide us specialized content (“Co-Branded Areas”). Such Co-Branded Areas will identify the third party. If you elect to register for the products and/or services provided at these Co-Branded Areas, you either will be providing your personal information to both us and the third party, or we might be providing your personal information directly to the third party.
Your personal information will be subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the privacy policy and practices of such third party. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those third parties and we suggest you review the respective privacy policies of those third parties to learn more about their privacy practices.
Mobile Data
When you access the Services on a mobile Device, we may use the information collected for any purpose set forth in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use the information to provide you with location-based Services, such as advertising, search results, and other personalized content. If you agree to have your Geo-location collected, we may use and retain that precise location data to provide you with information about our Services or carry out marketing and other activities contemplated by this Policy.
Analyze and Aggregate Non-Personal Information
We use aggregate information about our users and non-personal information to analyze our Services and user behavior and prepare aggregated reports which we may share with third parties.
Promotional Communications
We may use your contact information to send you updates and communications about our products and services or other promotional communications, such as newsletters, emails, or special offers or share your information with our trusted marketing partners so they can send promotional offers to you (“Promotional Communications”).
If you wish to opt out of receiving Promotional Communications from us or our marketing partners or change your preferences for Promotional Communications, you may follow the instructions in Section 6 Choice and Opt-Out, set forth below.
Information from Other Sources
The information we collect may be combined with information from outside records (e.g., demographic information, navigation information, and additional contact information) that we have acquired in accordance with the law. We may also acquire information from other sources about your visits over time and across other third party websites, in order to serve more targeted advertising and content to you on the Services.
Legal Matters; Safety
We may, without your consent, access and disclose your information, any communications sent or received by you, and any other information that we may have about you or your account as may be permitted or required by law (including, but not limited to, court order or subpoena), or to prevent or investigate suspected fraud, violations of our Terms of Service, which we encourage you to read in conjunction with this Privacy Policy, or activity that appears to us to be illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Additionally, we may disclose your information in situations that we believe may involve potential threats to the physical safety of any person or property.
Sale or Transfer of Business or Assets
If Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders, O.C.B.S. or any of its affiliated companies or businesses is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, Information of our users may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction. Information about our users may also be disclosed in connection with a commercial transaction where we are or any one of our businesses is seeking financing, investment, and support or funding.
Transactional Communications
We may use your information to send you notices from time to time relating to your account or your purchases. These may include order confirmations, invoices or customer service notifications. We may also send you Service-related announcements when it is necessary to do so; for instance, if our Service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, or the delivery of a product is delayed or there are policy changes.
5. ACCESS TO AND MANAGING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.
We believe it is important for you to be able to access and manage the information you have provided to us and make choices about how it is used. To inquire about or update your information, or change your preferences, you may take the following measures:
To cancel a subscription or membership or close your account, contact customer service at Support@OhioSteelheaders.com.
You may also contact us as set forth in Section 7 below.
6. EMAIL SELECTION AND OPT OUT
Opting Out of Promotional Messages
You may choose not to receive our Promotional Communications.
For emails, follow the “opt out” or “unsubscribe” instructions in promotional emails we send to you.
You may also contact us as set forth in Section 7 below.
Administrative Messages
You may not opt-out of administrative e-mails (for example e-mails about your account, transactions or policy changes) for your account.
Timing and Third Parties
We will endeavor to comply with your request for changes as soon as reasonably possible; please note that changes requested may not be effective immediately. Email opt-out requests may take up to 10 days to process. Unless required by law, we are not responsible for informing third parties with whom we have already shared your information of any changes requested pursuant to this section, or for removing information from or causing information to be removed from the databases or records of such entities.
7. IMPORTANT DISCLOSURES, PRACTICES
Links to Other Sites
Our Services may utilize hyperlinks to access external or third party sites, which are not controlled by us and therefore not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of those third party sites to determine how the proprietors of those sites will utilize your information.
Security
We implement security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. We use “Secure Socket Layers” or SSL to protect your personal information when collecting and transmitting your billing information to our payment processor. However, despite our efforts, no system can completely guarantee that there will never be unauthorized access to your personal information, and your use of our Services indicates that you are willing to assume this risk.
Storage and Retention
Information that you provide to us in the course of requesting a product or service through the Services may be gathered and stored in one or more of our corporate databases. Your personal information is stored for the length of time you have an account and for legitimate business purposes as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
We may retain some information from closed accounts or cancelled subscriptions or memberships so that we can comply with law, prevent fraud, assist with investigations, resolve disputes, analyze or troubleshoot programs, enforce our Terms of Service, or take other actions permitted by law. If your account or membership is terminated or suspended, we may also maintain some information to prevent re-registration.
A Note to International Users
The Services are hosted in the United States. If you are using the Services from outside the United States, you are consenting to the transfer of your information to the United States for processing and maintenance in accordance with this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. You are also consenting to the application of United States law in all matters concerning the Services.
Children’s Privacy
The Services are directed to an adult audience. We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under 18 years of age and, if we obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 18 years of age, we will take steps to remove that user’s personal information from our systems.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
We may change and update this Privacy Policy from time to time. You agree that we may notify you about material changes in the way we treat information by placing a notice on the Services. The most recent version of the Privacy Policy will always be posted on the Services, with the “Effective Date” posted at the top. You should check the Services frequently for updates. By accessing the Services after the Effective Date, you are deemed to consent to our then-current privacy policy.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83, known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us a list of what personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year and the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge. To make such a request, please contact us at Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders; Support@OhioSteelheaders.com. For all requests, you must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the body of your request, as well as your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. In the body of your request, please provide enough information for us to determine if this applies to you. You need to attest to the fact that you are a California resident, provide a valid, current California ID, and indicate a return address for our response. Please note that we will not accept requests via the telephone, mail, or by facsimile, and we are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or that do not have complete information.
Disputes
If you choose to visit the Services, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms including arbitration, limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the laws of the United States and the State of Ohio.
Contacting Us If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices email us at Support@OhioSteelheaders.com, or write to us at: Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders; OCBS  Box 29577  Parma, OH 44129.  When contacting us, please include your full name, address, phone number, and email address, and indicate the specific nature of your request.
Copyright © 2019 | Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders, L.L.C. | All rights reserved
Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders ~ Celebrating our 36th Anniversary in 2020
Paul DeunkBob HajekJerry DarkasJeff LiskayMike DurkalecJohn Beedlow, Jr.John BrochureSteve BruggerDon Mathews
OCBS Meetings   OCBS News   OCBS Tournaments   Special Events
Copyright © Ohio Central Basin Steelheaders / OhioSteelheaders.com | All Rights Reserved | Privacy Policy | Terms of Use
Managed with FutuRealm
Close Menu
